(Sheldon:)with a built-in laser pointer.
(Sheldon:)No?
How about can cozies
(Sheldon:)emblazoned
with our university mascot?
(Sheldon:)Go, Beavers.
(Sheldon:)I'll be back.
(Howard:)Okay, let's try this one.
"Spherical Hankel function."
(Leonard:)Hold on.
(Leonard:)That's it!
(Howard:)Eureka!
(Raj:)Hey, we agreed when
it was "Eureka" time,
(Raj:)we were all gonna
say it together.
(Howard:)Fine.
(Howard:)Let's say it together.
(Raj:)No. The moment
has passed.
(Sheldon:)Greetings, gentlemen.
(Sheldon:)How goes your
little project?
(Howard:)You mean,
"Project Lenwoloppali"?
(Sheldon:)Ah, a combination
of all your names.
(Raj:)Very clever.
I assume "Koothranardowitz"
was taken?